<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Munki on Zack McCauley - WardsParadox</title>
    <link>https://wardsparadox.github.io/tags/munki/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Munki on Zack McCauley - WardsParadox</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 11:57:36 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wardsparadox.github.io/tags/munki/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Munki URL Redirector</title>
      <link>https://wardsparadox.github.io/2019/09/munki-url-redirector/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 11:57:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wardsparadox.github.io/2019/09/munki-url-redirector/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Due to recent requests by staff who are struggling to find software in the Managed Software Center, I tried to find a way to send links to the users via email when they have requested. We use GSuite for Education, and Gmail will strip any links that have custom URL Schemes (like what Munki uses &lt;code&gt;munki://&lt;/code&gt;) for security reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Packages and Munki</title>
      <link>https://wardsparadox.github.io/2018/10/google-packages-and-munki/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wardsparadox.github.io/2018/10/google-packages-and-munki/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On a few machines, I&#39;ve been getting Munki errors related to the Chrome Remote Desktop Host update packages, and the Google Drive FileStream packages. The packages fail when you disable the Keystone Agent via Profile or via the MasterDisable key in &lt;code&gt;/Library/Preferences/com.google.Keystone.plist&lt;/code&gt;. As we deploy these updates through Munki via AutoPkg, I found that I needed to disable the GoogleSoftwareUpdate package bundled with both of these.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up MunkiReport-PHP on Ubuntu 16 with Nginx</title>
      <link>https://wardsparadox.github.io/2018/02/setting-up-munkireport-php-on-ubuntu-16-with-nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wardsparadox.github.io/2018/02/setting-up-munkireport-php-on-ubuntu-16-with-nginx/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This post is still really rough, but should be fully functional.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faster Munki Downloads from Nginx</title>
      <link>https://wardsparadox.github.io/2018/01/faster-munki-downloads-from-nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wardsparadox.github.io/2018/01/faster-munki-downloads-from-nginx/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Through multiple issues over the last month or so, I decided to completely rebuild my Munki server. This server is semi-critical in our district as all configurations are now sent out via Munki. As I was waiting for Ubuntu 16 to install and do some base configurations, I started looking for some guides on how to increase performance. I stumbled across &lt;a href=&#34;http://nginx.org/en/docs/ngx_core_module.html#worker_cpu_affinity&#34;&gt;worker_cpu_affinity&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying DetectX Swift with Munki</title>
      <link>https://wardsparadox.github.io/2018/01/deploying-detectx-swift-with-munki/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wardsparadox.github.io/2018/01/deploying-detectx-swift-with-munki/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DetectX Swift is an alternative to MalwareBytes Anti-Malware and was more economical for our district to use. It also is faster and more what we were looking for. I highly recommend it! This is a write up based on how we are deploying it here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding a &#34;Coming Soon&#34; Ribbon to the Munki Showcase</title>
      <link>https://wardsparadox.github.io/2015/12/adding-a-coming-soon-ribbon-to-the-munki-showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wardsparadox.github.io/2015/12/adding-a-coming-soon-ribbon-to-the-munki-showcase/</guid>
      <description>I have been doing some testing and it seems that with the latest OS X El Capitan release, our district can finally move to El Capitan. At the same time I have been doing some testing of Office 2016 for Mac. I have been moving our district to deploying software with Munki. It&#39;s been two years and has already saved us hundreds of man hours.
I was aware of the conditional items ability with Munki.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>